Guide to the Michael M. Dawida Papers, 1984-1995 AIS.2000.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- "Senate Journal" Television Program, 1989-1995; V.
  - "Senate Journal" with Senator Dawida, Topic: Special Session on Crime, March 27, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - "Senate Journal" with Senator Dawida, Topic: Special Session on Crime, Phase 2, August 26, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - "Senate Journal" with Senator Dawida, Topic: The Budget, April 19, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - "Senate Journal" with Senator Dawida, Topic: Education in Pennsylvania, June 26, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - "Senate Journal" with Senator Dawida, Topic: Military and Veterans Affairs, August 25, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - "Senate Journal" with Senator Dawida, Topic: From the Welfare Rolls to Payrolls, September 26, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - "Senate Journal" with Senator Dawida, Topic: Growing Older and Feeling Better, October 25, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - "Senate Journal" with Senator Dawida, Topic: A Farewell Tribute, November 14, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Media Appearances, 1988-1995; VI.
  This series dates between 1988 and 1995 and is arranged chronologically. It features appearances Senator Dawida made on television news segments, public service announcements, and as guests on talk shows. All material in this series is on VHS cassette tapes and can be viewed at the Archives Service Center.
  - Anti-Smoking Bill Signing, December 21, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - "Recharge Southside Steel", undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - "Senator Dawida News Conference", January 1, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - "Tourism '90 Pittsburgh", undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Capital Connection, Topic: Tourism in Pennsylvania, June 21, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Report to the People with Senator Porterfield, Topic: Tourism in Pennsylvania, June 27, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - "Maglev-Version I: A Clear Road to the Future", undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - "Maglev. 1. Technology and System; 2. Hamburg to Berlin", undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - "Capital Connection, Topic: Energy and Energy Conservation", October 2, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - "Capital Connection, Topic: Consumer Issues", November 13, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - "Capital Connection, Topic: Health Issues in PA", January 14, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - "Capitol Connection, Topic: Pennsylvania Treasury Department", March 19, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Senator Dawida "Mortgage Hotline PSA", undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - "Capitol Connection, Topic: Child Care in Pennsylvania", May 14, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - "Greater Pittsburgh Food Bank #2 PSA with Senator Dawida", undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - "Food Bank PSAs and Food Bank Package and Raw Video", undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - "Capitol Connection, Topic: Innovations in Education", October 22, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - "Capitol Connection, Topic: Worker's Compensation Reform in Pennsylvania", December 23, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - "Capitol Connection, Topic: Innovations in Education", October 22, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - "Capitol Connection, Topic: Worker's Compensation Reform in Pennsylvania", December 23, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - "Capitol Connection, Topic: Can you afford to be sick? The rising cost of Health Insurance", February 11, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - "Senate Journal" with Senator Jeanette Reibman, Topic: Can you afford to be sick? The rising cost of Health Insurance", March 10, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - "Report to the People with Senator Gene Porterfield, Topic: Can you afford to be sick? The rising cost of Health Insurance", March 31, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - "Capitol Connection, Topic: Pennsylvania Emergency Management Agency", May 22, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - "Capitol Connection, Topic: Transportation in Pennsylvania", August 25, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - "Capitol Connection, Topic: Economic Impact of Sports in PA", September 28, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - "Capitol Connection, Topic: Pennsylvania's Recycling Effort- The New Frontier", December 15, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - "Workers' Compensation Fraud", undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - "Capitol Connection, Topic: PA Minority Business Development Authority", January 25, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - "Capitol Connection, Topic: State of the Commonwealth", February 25, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - "Pennsylvania/ International Partners in Progress PSA", undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - "Capitol Connection, Topic: Children's Health Problems and Issues", April 28, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - PSA for Greater Pittsburgh Community Food Bank, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - "Capitol Connections, Topic: Curbing Crime in Pennsylvania, ", November 23, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - "Pennsylvania International Partners In Progress" PSA, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - "Capital Connection, Topic: Health Issues of the Future, ", January 3, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Media Coverage 1993, Regional Assets District (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - "Senator Mike Dawida Senate Chamber Farewell Remarks", December 13, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - "PACE Program with Senator Mike Dawida" PSA, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)